{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A brace","incorrectAnswers":["A murder","A shoal","A nye"],"question":"What is the word for a group of bucks?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Queen Isabella I","incorrectAnswers":["Queen Eleanor II","Queen Margot III","Queen Sera IV"],"question":"Which influential Queen of Castille helped create a powerful and unified state of Spain, whose influence spread to the Americas?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Red wine","incorrectAnswers":["Brandy","Port","Beer"],"question":"What type of alcohol is traditionally used in the French dish 'Coq au Vin'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Russia","incorrectAnswers":["Cambodia","Vietnam","Uzbekistan"],"question":"Borscht is a dish that is most associated with which part of the world?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Red Hot Chili Peppers","incorrectAnswers":["The Monkees","Black Flag","Journey"],"question":"Which American rock band released the album 'Blood Sugar Sex Magik'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Indo-European","incorrectAnswers":["Uralic","Afroasiatic","Niger–Congo"],"question":"The language 'Maithili' belongs to which language family?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Winston Churchill","incorrectAnswers":["Clement Atlee","Tony Blair","Neville Chamberlain"],"question":"Which former British prime minister returned to power in 1951?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"1","incorrectAnswers":["Red","5","Black"],"question":"What is the highest level of readiness for the military when using the DEFCON system?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Danny DeVito","incorrectAnswers":["Ben Kingsley","Michael Douglas","Kiefer Sutherland"],"question":"Which actor has featured in films including Men in Black and One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Muse","incorrectAnswers":["Tears for Fears","Bullet For My Valentine","Enter Shikari"],"question":"Which English rock band released the studio album 'Showbiz'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Crystal Cubism","incorrectAnswers":["Abstract expressionism","post-impressionism","Modernism"],"question":"The painting \"Three Musicians\" by Pablo Picasso is a part of which art movement?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Rio De Janeiro","incorrectAnswers":["Caracas","San Juan","Montevideo"],"question":"Which of these cities is in Brazil?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Clint Eastwood","incorrectAnswers":["James Cagney","Marlon Brando","Harrison Ford"],"question":"Which actor played the role of Blondie in The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Harold Wilson","incorrectAnswers":["Clement Atlee","Anthony Eden","Margaret Thatcher"],"question":"Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"The Treasure of the Sierra Madre","incorrectAnswers":["Terms of Endearment","The Maltese Falcon","The Birds"],"question":"Which film contains the character 'Fred C. Dobbs'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Erosion","incorrectAnswers":["Sediment","Vegetation","Sublimation"],"question":"By what process is rock worn down by the weather?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"2 Turtle Doves","incorrectAnswers":["2 Ladies Dancing","2 Fresh Apples","2 Mocking Birds"],"question":"What did 'my true love give to me' on the second day of Christmas?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Chairman of the Board","incorrectAnswers":["The Voice","Ol' Blue Eyes","King of Swing"],"question":"Which nickname for Frank Sinatra highlights his role as a powerful figure in the music industry, much like a corporate CEO?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"The Rolling Stones","incorrectAnswers":["McFly","Delirious?","Depeche Mode"],"question":"Which English rock band released the studio album 'Sticky Fingers'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"United Arab Emirates","incorrectAnswers":["Faeroe Islands","Israel","Armenia"],"question":"Which region of the world uses '.ae' at the end of its web addresses?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Agatha Christie","incorrectAnswers":["Robert Louis Stevenson","Charles Dickens","Lewis Carroll"],"question":"Which author wrote 'The Murder of Roger Ackroyd'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Monopoly","incorrectAnswers":["Life","Risk","Chess"],"question":"What is the name of the classic board game where players must collect properties and build houses and hotels?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Macarena","incorrectAnswers":["Rico Suave","Take on Me","Cum on Feel the Noize"],"question":"Los Del Rio had a one hit wonder in 1996 with which song?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Dam","incorrectAnswers":["Clam","Scam","Lamb"],"question":"What is a barrier that blocks flowing water?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Addis Ababa","incorrectAnswers":["Bishkek","Chisinau","Sana'a"],"question":"What is the capital city of Ethiopia?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Real Madrid","incorrectAnswers":["Manchester United","AC Milan","Liverpool"],"question":"Which club was the first to win two consecutive Champions League titles?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"6 Geese A Laying","incorrectAnswers":["6 Maids a Milking","6 Gold Rings","6 Drummers Drumming"],"question":"What did 'my true love give to me' on the sixth day of Christmas?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Poison Ivy","incorrectAnswers":["Oak","Sumac","Jimsonweed"],"question":"What plant's oil, called urushiol, causes skin irritation when it comes into contact with human skin?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"3 meters","incorrectAnswers":["2 meters","1 meter","4 meters"],"question":"What is the height of a basketball hoop in competitions?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Hexagon","incorrectAnswers":["Pentagon","Octagon","Triangle"],"question":"What is the name of a shape with six sides?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Steve Buscemi","incorrectAnswers":["Christopher Lee","Arnold Schwarzenegger","Anthony Hopkins"],"question":"Which Hollywood actor has featured in TV shows including The Sopranos and Boardwalk Empire?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"The Industrial Revolution","incorrectAnswers":["The French Revolution","The American Revolution","The Enlightenment"],"question":"What was the major economic revolution that started in the 18th century?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Black Eyed Peas","incorrectAnswers":["MercyMe","Three 6 Mafia","The Velvet Underground"],"question":"Which American band released the song 'Boom Boom Pow'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Henry Ford","incorrectAnswers":["Carl Benz","Rudolf Diesel","Gottlieb Daimler"],"question":"Who introduced the Model T in 1908, the first inexpensive car for the masses?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Kate Winslet","incorrectAnswers":["Kathy Bates","Kirsten Dunst","Sandra Bæ Hovedr"],"question":"Which actress has starred in films including Titanic and Finding Neverland?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Porcine","incorrectAnswers":["Bovine","Mammalian","Recombinant"],"question":"Horse Is To Equine As Pig Is To What?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Wood","incorrectAnswers":["Fossils","Handwriting","Mountains"],"question":"What is Xylology the study of?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Longinus","incorrectAnswers":["Atticus","Augustus","Tiberius"],"question":"Which Roman soldier pierced the crucified Christ on His side with his spear.","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Jakarta","incorrectAnswers":["Yaounde","Singapore","Kuala Lumpur"],"question":"What is the capital city of Indonesia?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Nancy Sinatra","incorrectAnswers":["Lulu","Louis Armstrong","Billie Eilish"],"question":"Who performed the theme song to the James Bond film You Only Live Twice?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Abraham Lincoln","incorrectAnswers":["George Washington","Ronald Regan","Thomas Jefferson"],"question":"Who proclaimed Thanksgiving a national holiday in the USA in 1863?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Israel","incorrectAnswers":["Ukraine","Pakistan","Turkey"],"question":"Jerusalem is the capital city of which country?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Tempera","incorrectAnswers":["Watercolor","Pastel","Dadaism"],"question":"What is the word for a painting technique using pigments mixed with egg yolk and water?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"The Seychelles","incorrectAnswers":["Madagascar","Indonesia","The Bahamas"],"question":"Which Islands In The Indian Ocean Gained Their Independence From Britain In 1976?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Michael Jackson","incorrectAnswers":["Nicki Minaj","Neil Young","Eric Clapton"],"question":"'Black or White' was sung by which musician?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"The Fugees","incorrectAnswers":["N.E.R.D","No Doubt","All Saints"],"question":"With Which Band Did Wyclef Jean & Lauryn Hill First Make Their Name?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Jim Carrey","incorrectAnswers":["Gerard Butler","Hugh Jackman","Michael Fassbender"],"question":"Which actor has starred in films including Batman Forever and The Truman Show?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"\"Louis, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.\"","incorrectAnswers":["\"Here's Johnny!\"","\"I love lamp.\"","\"Gentlemen, you can't fight in here! This is the War Room!\""],"question":"Which of these quotes is from the film 'Casablanca'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Ural","incorrectAnswers":["Alps","Pyrenees","Atlas"],"question":"Which mountain range is regarded as the Eastern border of Europe?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A herd","incorrectAnswers":["A watch","A murder","A muster"],"question":"What is the word for a group of goats?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Niger–Congo","incorrectAnswers":["Uralic","Austronesian","Dravidian"],"question":"The language 'Kinyarwanda' belongs to which language family?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Louis XVI","incorrectAnswers":["Louis XIII","Charles VIII","Charles XI"],"question":"Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Lauryn Hill - The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill","incorrectAnswers":["Salt-N-Pepa - Hot, Cool & Vicious","Missy Elliott - Supa Dupa Fly","Nicki Minaj - Pink Friday"],"question":"Who was the first female rapper to have a solo album certified diamond (10 million sales in the USA) by the RIAA?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Rocks","incorrectAnswers":["Diseases of the lungs","Human movement","Light waves"],"question":"What is Lithology the study of?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Nevada","incorrectAnswers":["Arizona","Colorado","Alaska"],"question":"Which U.S. state has the least rainfall?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Because the Night","incorrectAnswers":["Let's Spend the Night Together","Borderline","Nobody's Fault But Mine"],"question":"Which song, originally recorded by Patti Smith, was later covered by Bruce Springsteen?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Golf","incorrectAnswers":["Figure skating","Football","Volleyball"],"question":"With which sport is Jack Nicklaus associated?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Cantaloupe","incorrectAnswers":["Mango","Kiwi","Banana"],"question":"Which of these fruits is a type of  melon?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Operation VICTOR V","incorrectAnswers":["Operation Flashpoint","Operation Ketsugo","Operation Ten-Go"],"question":"What was the name of the operation in 1945 to liberate the Philippines?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Baroque","incorrectAnswers":["Abstract expressionism","Ukiyo-e","Cubism"],"question":"The painting \"Massacre of the Innocents\" by Peter Paul Rubens is a part of which art movement?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"The Hoover Dam","incorrectAnswers":["The Three Gorges Dam","The Oroville Dam","The Theodore Roosevelt Dam"],"question":"Which Dam Harnesses The Colorado River","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Starland Vocal Band","incorrectAnswers":["The Galaxy Quartet","Sirens of Titan","The Milky Ways"],"question":"'Afternoon Delight' was the only major hit for which one-hit-wonder group?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Sequoia","incorrectAnswers":["Redbud","Oak","Maple"],"question":"What is the name of the tree that can reach up to 350 feet tall and is named after a region in California?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"The Thing","incorrectAnswers":["Jurassic Park","V for Vendetta","Monsters, Inc."],"question":"Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A research team in Antarctica is hunted by a shape-shifting alien.'","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Crash Test Dummies","incorrectAnswers":["Cheryl Lynn","Minnie Riperton","Buster Poindexter"],"question":"Who had a hit in 1993 with Mmm Mmm Mmm Mmm?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"The Doors","incorrectAnswers":["Styx","The Pussycat Dolls","Three 6 Mafia"],"question":"Which American rock band released the song 'People Are Strange'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Arno","incorrectAnswers":["Severn","Seine","Tagus"],"question":"What river separates the city of Florence?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Québec","incorrectAnswers":["Phoenix","Minneapolis-St Paul","Denver"],"question":"Which of these cities is in Canada?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"The Beatles","incorrectAnswers":["Deep Purple","Feeder","Uriah Heep"],"question":"Which English rock band released the studio album 'Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band'?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Lung","incorrectAnswers":["Heart","Liver","Brain"],"question":"In which organ is a pulmonary disease located?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Lion","incorrectAnswers":["Bat","Owl","Bull"],"question":"Which animal would you associate with the ING Group logo?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"\"No wire hangers, ever!\"","incorrectAnswers":["\"That’s a bingo!\"","\"Toto, I've a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.\"","\"I’m not drinking any f****** Merlot!\""],"question":"Which of these quotes is from the film 'Mommie Dearest'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Periods","incorrectAnswers":["Cycles","Eons","Stratas"],"question":"Geological eras are divided into units called ________.","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Zagreb","incorrectAnswers":["Rabat","Ashgabat","Niamey"],"question":"What is the capital city of Croatia?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A Hembra","incorrectAnswers":["A Nanny","A Jenny","A Leopardess"],"question":"A female llama is known as what?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Google","incorrectAnswers":["Nokia","PlayStation","Panasonic"],"question":"Which technology brand is associated with the marketing slogan 'Don't Be Evil'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Georges Seurat","incorrectAnswers":["Caravaggio","Gustav Klimt","‎Pablo Picasso"],"question":"Which artist painted \"A Sunday Afternoon on the Island of La Grande Jatte\"","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Shanghai Tower","incorrectAnswers":["Petronas Towers","Taipei 101","Burj Khalifa"],"question":"What is the name of China's tallest skyscraper?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Guns N' Roses","incorrectAnswers":["MercyMe","The Pussycat Dolls","Three 6 Mafia"],"question":"Which American hard rock band released the song 'Paradise City'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Manhattan Island","incorrectAnswers":["The Moon","The Last Dodo","Queen Elizabeth's Corpse"],"question":"What did Peter Minuit buy in 1626?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Inception","incorrectAnswers":["A Beautiful Mind","The Sixth Sense","A Clockwork Orange"],"question":"Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A thief who steals secrets through dreams must plant an idea into the mind of a C.E.O.'","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Gdansk","incorrectAnswers":["Stuttgart","Amsterdam","Paris"],"question":"Which of these cities is in Poland?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Entomology","incorrectAnswers":["Botany","Zoology","Horticulture"],"question":"What Is The Study Of Insects Called? ","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Franklin Roosevelt","incorrectAnswers":["Dwight Eisenhower","Lyndon B. Johnson","Harry Truman"],"question":"Who Was President Of The USA At The Outbreak Of World War II?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Dead Sea","incorrectAnswers":["Black Sea","Mediterranean Sea","Tasman Sea"],"question":"Which is the only sea below sea level?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"The Big Sleep","incorrectAnswers":["The Wind in the Willows","The Thin Man","Ulysses"],"question":"Which book contains the character 'Philip Marlowe'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Rontgen","incorrectAnswers":["Curie","Einstein","Maxwell"],"question":"Who discovered x-rays in 1895?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Figure skating","incorrectAnswers":["Ice hockey","Gymnastics","Tennis"],"question":"Which sport saw athletes like John Curry and Peggy Fleming rise to prominence as proteges of coach Carlo Fassi?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Tracy Ullman","incorrectAnswers":["Vanessa Phillips","Paula Skeeberg","Mary Myers"],"question":"Name the female comedy star who once had a show on Fox, that had a pop hit in the early eighties","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Battered","incorrectAnswers":["Poached","Crumbled","Spatchcock"],"question":"What word is used when food is coated in a mixture of flour and eggs for frying?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"ABBA","incorrectAnswers":["The Beach Boys","Atomic Kitten","Spice Girls"],"question":"Which pop group released the album 'Voulez-Vous'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Uma Thurman","incorrectAnswers":["Penélope Cruz","Kirsten Dunst","Kristin Scott Thomas"],"question":"Which actress has starred in films including Pulp Fiction and Batman & Robin?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Adriatic","incorrectAnswers":["Baltic","Aegean","Black"],"question":"What sea is to the east of Italy?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Moon River","incorrectAnswers":["Yellow River","Blue River","Styx River"],"question":"Which musical river was described as \"wider than a mile\" and as belonging to \"my huckleberry friend\"?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Heartbreak Hotel'l","incorrectAnswers":["Hound Dog","Jailhouse Rock","Love Me Tender"],"question":"What was the name of the first of Elvis Presley's 114 Top 40 hits?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Safety Dance","incorrectAnswers":["What's Up","Bitch","I Know What Boys Like"],"question":"What song did Men Without Hats have a hit with in 1983?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Orange","incorrectAnswers":["Blue","Gold","Maroon"],"question":"Which of these colors is included on the flag of Cote d'Ivoire?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Jay Gatsby","incorrectAnswers":["Holden Caulfield","Atticus Finch","Scout Finch"],"question":"Which literary character lives in West Egg, Long Island, and is known by the nickname 'the Great'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Andre Agassi","incorrectAnswers":["Roger Federer","Tim Henman","Fred Perry"],"question":"Who in 2003 aged 33 became the oldest male tennis player to be number one in the ATP's entry rankings?","difficulty":"hard"},